

## INFO

→ GitHul

@DmitryHordyna

in LinkedIn

Dmytro Hordyno

Mai Mai

hordynadmytro@gmail.com

Phone

O Area

# **TECH SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Adaptability
- Flexibility
- Teamwork
- Energy
- A sense of humor

## **SPOKEN LANGUAGES**

- English B1
- Ukraine Native speaker
- Russian Advance

#### HOBBIES

Socialising with firends and family, playing football, reading books ,cycling bicycle,computing and also travaling

# Hordyna Dmytro

Full-Stack Developer

#### **ABOUT ME**

At the moment I am studying on the GoIT course, specializing in Full-Stack Developer. The training provides a lot of tech-skills practice, participation in team projects and IT English. At this stage, I am completing the Javascript and React course and now studying Node JS. My goal is to become a Middle Front End Developer in two years. Open to internships and vacancies for junior.

#### **PROJECTS**

Event Booster [ HTML5, CSS3, JS, Webpack] An application for finding actual events in the world.

The Founder [ JavaScript ] An application to search for a picture by name.

Phonebook [ React ] Application with authorization, where you can save your contacts.

Ice-cream [ HTML5, CSS3, Parcel ] A website with a responsive layout.

Web Studio [ HTML5, CSS3 ] A website with a responsive layout.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Internship from the university agricultural practices

May 2019 - December 2021 Denmark

Adaptation to a new environment.

Willingness to take on any challenge

Daily communication in English.

# Design engineer

June 2017 - December 2018 | Ukraine

Draw details car using Compas 3D and SolidWorks.

Monitoring and updating of documents.

# **EDUCATION**

National University of Life and Environmental Sciences of Ukraine

Septermber 2013 - December 2018 | Ukraine

Design engineer (Master)

## **ADDITIONAL EDUCATION**

Rolling Scopes School

July 2021 - till now | Online

Front-End Developer

GOIT School

Septermber 2020 - till now Online

Full-Stack Developer